Babe, what are you doing?
I'm looking for
the aloe iodine.
It's not here.
Yeah, because that's
not where it is.
Babe, c-can you give me
12 seconds,
and I will come
and get it for you?
Twelve seconds is specific.
Wow, these are very expired.
Hmm.
Okay. Betadine.
Chlorhexidine.
No iodine.
Oh. Right. Thanks.
But...
Well, that's not...
We tried for two years.
I know. I know, babe.
I mean, we don't wanna even
talk about it anymore.
Talking was not
the important part.
It wasn't gonna be for us, and
we were okay with that.
- We were okay, but...
- Mm-hmm.
Well...
This is better.
Yes. It's...
- It's a lot better, isn't it?
- This is great.
Obviously,
we're gonna need protocols
to account for
our cell mutations...
No, Reed.
...monitoring for
further cosmic effects.
Reed.
We can do this.
Okay?
I really want to do this.
Then what?
Nothing is going to change.
Of course not.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we welcome you
to a very special event
celebrating four years of
the Fantastic Four.
And now your host
for the evening, Ted Gilbert.
Well, now, folks.
Folks, we all know the story.
Four brave astronauts
head up into space,
encounter a bit of
cosmic turbulence,
and come back forever changed.
Not just the molecules
of their bodies
but also their place
in our hearts.
And, now, a look back.
This is
Excelsior Launch Control.
T-minus 3 hours, 42 minutes,
19 seconds.
Four years ago,
man and woman conquered the
last frontier as we know it,
the exploration of space.
The best pilot in the world
right here.
Yeah. The best-looking
he means.
It was my mission:
Space exploration.
I assembled the best
scientific minds
to come along,
who also happened to be
my best friend,
my wife
and my brother-in-law.
Comms check.
Everybody, sound off.
- Check.
- Check, check.
- Comms are live.
That last voice you just heard
was my baby brother,
Jonathan Storm,
and, ladies,
he is very single.
- Kiss for luck.
- Kiss?
However,
Dr. Richards's expedition
encountered
an unforeseen event
that changed
not only the lives
of these
courageous individuals...
Verify go for launch.
Go for launch.
...but also
the course of our history.
- Come in, Excelsior.
- What is that?
I don't know. I don't know.
It must be the cosmic rays.
- Ben! Ben!
- Ben!
Obviously,
while we were in space
due to errors on my part...
- Stop.
- ...we encountered
a cosmic storm
that altered our DNA.
Rescue in progress
of the Excelsior launch.
We came back with anomalies.
And they
returned with superpowers.
They became our protectors.
Cannonball!
It's clobberin' time!
Hmm.
I was at the opening
of the Pan Am Tower
when Mole Man attacked.
The Fantastic Four
saved my life.
Mole Man's attempt
to steal the Pan Am building
was thwarted
by the Fantastic Four.
This is all
Reed Richards's fault.
Him and his endless pursuit
of progress.
Power to the underground!
And when the Mad Thinker
tried to sabotage
New York City
the Fantastic Four
came to our rescue.
Gotcha!
Have a great day!
They defeated Red Ghost
and his Super-Apes.
They became our inspiration.
This equation not only
confirms alternate dimensions,
but it suggests
parallel Earths
exist on different
dimensional planes.
Who wants to see
a big explosion?
Me!
And they became our leaders.
Sue Storm brokers
peace deal
with Harvey "Mole Man" Elder,
leader of the underground
nation, Subterranea.
I don't trust
surface dwellers.
I never have.
But I do trust Sue.
We have come together today
to form a new charter,
the Future Foundation.
All participating
countries agree
to dismantle
their armed forces.
And on
this fourth anniversary,
we celebrate them.
They are the very best of us.
They are the Fantastic Four.
Thank you, Fantastic Four!
- Thank you, Fantastic Four!
- We love you, Fantastic Four.
- I love you, Johnny!
- We love you!
- Thank you, Fantastic Four.
We are proud to
call them our guides,
our protectors
and our friends.
Let's hear it for Reed, Sue,
Johnny and Ben.
I must say, that
was all a bit aggrandizing.
- Yeah.
- H.E.R.B.I.E.
H.E.R.B.I.E. with the herbs.
How's that sauce looking?
Don't do that.
Wash your hands first, please.
I was wearing my gloves
the whole time.
Just wash your hands.
Let me try that.
Okay.
Okay. Is this guy good?
That is fantastic.
- Oh, let me try.
- It's incredible stuff.
Stop. Don't do that.
Don't do that.
It's not quite done.
No, it's not quite done.
No, it could be done,
but I'm gonna add
a little more garlic.
Not because
it's not delicious.
I just want to add
a little bit of zip, okay?
What are you doing?
What do you mean,
what am I doing?
I mean, you're gonna
ruin your appetite.
I'm hungry.
They're never late
for Sunday dinner.
Should we wait?
I guess.
You're late.
What, uh- What do you mean?
What do you mean,
what do I mean?
You're late for dinner.
Oh. Yes, we are.
We're late for dinner.
- By a single minute.
- Yes, we were just...
I had to put some aloe iodine
on my shoulder and...
...just had to do
his shoulder and...
Why is there breakfast cereal
on the dinner table?
Why are you being weird?
- We're not being weird.
- We're not acting weird.
You're doing that
weird thing with your face.
Well, we don't know
what you're talking about.
Are you pregnant?
- Yeah, we're pregnant.
- Yes, yes.
How did you know that?
Have you looked at
your husband's face?
I know.
He just cannot keep a secret.
- Wait, what? Really?
- Yeah.
What?
You are gonna be the best mom.
Oh, my God.
And you are gonna be
the best dad.
Just kidding.
You are out of your depth.
But we... we're gonna be
the best uncles ever.
Okay, we should eat.
You're handling this well,
you know.
I figured you'd be
locked in your lab
drenched in a panic sweat.
I have that
scheduled for later.
Countdown continues
as the Fantastic Four
prepare to welcome
a new member to the family.
Needless to say, preparations
inside the Baxter Building
are well underway.
All right, H.E.R.B.I.E.,
let's start the baby prep.
H.E.R.B.I.E.!
Yancy Street bookies
are putting the odds
of a girl at 4-to-5,
but chances of twins
are a long shot.
Herbert!
H.E.R.B.I.E.!
The oil and gas cowboys
want a minute to yell at you
before you go
on maternity leave.
Speaking of, coal lobby.
Lynne, when you see Sue, can-
Larry, I will tell her
when I see her.
Thank you, Lynne.
The question
on everybody's mind is,
"Will the baby be born
with superpowers?"
H.E.R.B.I.E.,
we need to scan the baby.
The Interna-Scan
hasn't achieved
the right level of precession
for clear imaging.
New deep space transmission?
Let's identify its origin.
Shall we record and file it?
Mm-hmm.
2:15? What 2:15? I don't have
any meetings today.
Ah, Reed.
Oh, that 2:15.
Thank you for making the time.
Johnny, do we have to today?
I had some thoughts
on the new suit design.
There are no new suit designs.
You finished them years ago.
They have dust on them.
I get it. You're going
to be a father soon.
New responsibilities.
- You're a bit scared.
- I'm not scared.
I'm busy, Johnny.
I'm busy. I'm busy.
There's a difference.
New transmission today.
Have you listened to it yet?
More of the same.
It's a complex signal.
Knock yourself out.
Johnny, I'm running a test.
Cool.
I got time.
Bridge teleportation test.
Movement of organic matter,
six meters.
Thank you, Herbert.
Let's run it.
It worked.
- Johnny.
- Yep.
Could you reset the breaker?
Other way.
Babe?
Babe, when you're done,
can you...
Hello, H.E.R.B.I.E.
I, um...
I just went by the nursery.
How's it looking?
Um, it's looking like
H.E.R.B.I.E.'s
building the crib.
Which I kinda thought
was a you deal.
I built this instead.
Anyone can build a crib.
Only I can build this.
Anyone can build a crib
but not-not ours. Not for him.
This is for him.
Because unlike anyone else,
his parents have
cosmically compromised DNA.
Reed.
Reed, we have done every test.
Well, not this one.
You wanna see?
Fine. Let's see.
See? There's
nothing wrong with him.
He's absolutely perfect.
That is such a bullshit way
to win an argument.
- Happy Halloween.
Easy with the candy.
- Hi, Ben.
- Hi, Heather.
- Hey, Ben. How's Sue doing?
- Yeah, she's getting close.
She was craving
some Maisie's cookies.
Hey! What time is it?
Say the thing.
That's not really
something I say.
It's clobberin' time!
It's just in the cartoon.
Sorry, sir.
Oh, my God. There he is!
- Whoa, that's him!
- Hey! Lift the car!
You want me to lift up a car?
This car? Right here?
You guys are gonna
get me in trouble.
- Lift the car!
- I... I'll... I'll try.
Lift the car!
Can't do it.
- Come on, you can do it!
- I'll try one more time.
Lift the car! Lift the car!
Lift the car! Lift the...
Throw the car! Yeah, throw it!
- Throw the car?
- Yeah, throw the car.
Okay, everyone. Settle down.
Back to your game.
Hey, maybe throw it next time.
That'll show 'em.
No, no, no.
It's okay. I love kids.
Spend the day
with ten fourth-grade girls
and you may begin
to rethink that.
Rachel Rozman. Uh...
- I'm Ben.
- I know.
You grew up near on Yancy,
yeah?
Right there.
Oh. Very near.
You know, it feels
really good being back here.
I like that everything
stays the same.
Like Maisie's? The best.
The black-and-white cookies were always
my favorite when I was a kid, but...
we used to steal 'em
back then.
Okay. Well, maybe
step inside next time.
Kids would love to see ya.
Yeah. Okay. I will.
I'll bring cookies.
Oh, yeah? Okay.
Yeah, I'll bring cookies.
All right.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
It doesn't matter
how long you beat it.
You're not gonna make a
meringue if there's egg yolks.
The real question is, do you
add some vinegar or not?
I'm a vinegar guy.
Always have been.
Hey. Why the long face?
What of it?
Sounds like your 2:15
with Reed didn't go well.
I'm sorry, pal.
Hey, I'm fine, you know?
I don't mind. It's just, uh-
I hear ya.
We'll go to space again.
Yeah, we will.
Oh. Nice.
I'm Johnny Storm.
Flame on.
Flame on. Flame on. Flame-
Flame off.
Down.
Fantastic Kitchen, down.
- Whoops.
- Stop it.
I finished the crib.
Included two extras.
I don't know why.
Mmm. Thank you.
- Go time.
- No, it's okay.
This... This is me.
For the last few months,
I've been tracking
a small number
of criminal organizations.
A small number, huh?
Forty-seven of them,
including the Puppet Master
in the Bowery,
the Wizard in Gramercy Park
and Diablo
in Washington Heights.
You babyproofed the world.
- It's a sweet gesture.
- It's a thorough gesture.
But, uh, I like punching.
- You mean "clobbering"?
- No, I mean "punching."
- Let's eat.
- Hey, what time is it?
It's dinnertime. Get inside.
You sure
it's not clobbering time?
Stop it.
- Johnny.
- On it.
What the hell?
Would you look at that?
Stand clear. I need
everybody to remain calm
and clear the area.
- Stay back. Out of the way.
- Get back.
Out of the way.
Get back.
Breaking
news from Times Square.
There appears to be
an object in the sky,
debris raining down
and some sort...
Are you the protectors
of this world?
Yes, we are.
Your planet is now
marked for death.
Your world will be consumed
by The Devourer.
There is nothing
you can do to stop him.
For he is a universal force.
As essential as the stars.
Hold your loved ones close,
and speak the words
you've been afraid to speak.
Use this time to rejoice
and celebrate,
for your time is short.
I herald his beginning.
I herald your end.
I herald...
Galactus.
Whoa!
Scientists
around the world are trying
to verify the origin of this
unknown space creature...
Are you tracking her?
She is too fast to track,
Johnny.
She is too fast,
but I'm tracking
where she's been.
What's a Galactus? Right?
And how do you consume
a whole planet?
Here. DA-773, a planet
in the Proxima Delphi system.
- He ate that whole planet?
- Five planets, actually.
Five have disappeared,
that I'm aware of.
There might be more
that fit the pattern.
And the pattern is what?
That they've been chosen
with great care.
Targeted.
And not just disappeared.
Destroyed.
Wait, you're saying that
these planets disappearing,
- that's connected to her?
- Yes.
I've identified
the herald's energy signature
and matched it to DA-773.
She was there.
She was at all of them.
So you're saying
this Galactus...
Can do exactly
what she says it can do.
How long to get
Excelsior launch-ready?
Either we go up there
or Galactus comes here.
I don't know, 20 hours.
The launch window is in 16.
- Guys... Hey, guys.
- Like I said, 16 hours.
I'll start the nav plot.
Hey, guys...
H, you wanna
buzz the prep team
and I'll meet you down there?
Uh, she spoke to me.
The herald. She spoke to me.
She spoke to all of us,
Johnny.
Galactus, devouring...
Well, when I chased her,
she spoke to me
in her language.
What did she say?
Well, it was in her
own language. I don't know.
Well, what were
the context clues?
Context. Space.
And what was the tone?
Angry? Threatening?
No, no, no. Not at all.
It was, uh...
...kind.
Kind?
Not kind. Warm.
- Warm?
- I don't know. It was...
- She was, like, right here.
- Mm-hmm.
And I was looking into
her beautiful face,
and I saw stars,
and I could see me
in her face.
She spoke to me,
and it was kind of, um...
Warm?
Kind. Kind?
No. No. I get it.
Johnny loves space.
Johnny loves women.
Now there's a literal
naked space woman,
and Johnny thinks
they had a moment.
I doubt she was naked.
It was probably
a stellar polymer.
For the record,
Ben loves when Johnny speaks in third person.
We need to get ready.
Okay. So she spoke to you,
yeah? And?
There are 23 of these.
The only repeated language
and the oldest recordings.
Now, I don't know who they are
or what they're saying,
but this...
this is the same.
This is her language.
Okay. Maybe that is something.
Reed wants to see you
in the lab.
You summoned me.
I finally knocked it
off the list.
What?
The new space suits.
It's flame-retardant.
Maxed out oxygen supply,
but...
You have to monitor the gauge.
If you stay flamed on
in zero atmosphere,
you will burn through your air
reserves in less than ten minutes.
Oh.
I take back
every single bad thing
I've been saying about you.
To myself.
In private.
Four years ago,
we were dreamers.
Back then,
the unknown meant adventure,
and mystery, and discovery.
With space,
the greatest mystery of all.
The last occasion
led to the accident
that mutated them
and gave them those fan...
What we learned
was that the unknown
also meant fear.
And profound, radical change.
Hiya, pal.
Johnny showed me the new suit.
It's pretty spiffy, especially
compared to the old ones.
Well, the old ones...
weren't adequate.
Eh, who could've known?
Me.
- I could've known.
- Stop.
Please. You gotta stop beating
yourself up about this.
You know, Stretch,
I got bad news for you.
You ain't that smart.
Except I am that smart.
Oh, yeah? Can you cook?
It's more of an art,
not a science.
Did you pass
your driver's test?
That was due to
poorly marked signage.
Huh.
This Galactus, this herald,
they got no idea
what they're up against.
So the four of us
will return to space
and face the danger
waiting there,
and we will find
this Galactus.
The second the engines fire,
everything you do from then on
will be the first time
a pregnant woman
has done them
in the history of the world.
I know.
I really do.
And just because
I'm not talking about it
doesn't mean
I'm not thinking about it.
About him.
I really love my new suit.
It's really your old one,
it's just a lot bigger.
Bluer.
It is actually bluer.
Just a little extra
around the sides is all.
This is
Excelsior Launch Control.
T-minus two hours,
37 minutes, 20 seconds.
Here we stand prepared
to face a danger
that is unknown.
A danger that
has threatened our home,
threatened our families
and threatened this planet.
The unknown will become known,
and we will protect you.
We will protect you.
Final check and check, please.
- Check.
Check.
Twelve, eleven,
ten, nine, eight, seven...
Starting ignition sequence.
...six, five, four, three...
Go for launch.
...two, one.
The Excelsior has liftoff.
Whoo-hoo!
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a successful launch.
And from all of us on Earth,
we wish you good luck.
And Godspeed.
Thank you, Earth.
You seeing that?
Approaching the FTL engine.
Wait for my signal, Sue.
Yeah.
And three, two, one. Mark.
And we are locked.
And clear for FTL navigation.
Faster-than-light
in three, two, one.
So the herald's
energy signature tracks
to this binary system here.
LHS-275, yes.
Where we find her,
we find Galactus.
Reed, what are
we up against here?
Some sort of a space dragon
or something?
- Cool.
- We don't know.
But it's
basic tactical science.
Observe, assess capabilities,
have H.E.R.B.I.E. collect
any liquid, gas...
...solid materials,
analyze his physiology.
Look, if he's just
some big guy in a ship,
then yes,
you can punch him out.
Coming in on the dark side
of the system's larger planet.
Copy that.
I'm gonna take us out of FTL.
Okay, everyone. Be prepared.
So, where's this Galactus?
That's strange.
The herald's heat signature is
coming from inside the planet.
What the hell is happening
to that planet?
Is there something alive
down there?
What is that?
- Ben!
- I'm on it!
Dropping us out of FTL.
Watch out!
Sue, hide us!
It's all gone.
The whole planet.
And it was 13%
larger than Earth.
- Ben!
- It's not responding.
I'm locked out.
H.E.R.B.I.E., try to stabilize
the engines.
What's going on?
It's got us.
It's pulling us in.
Ben, save the engines.
Save the engine!
Johnny...
your girlfriend's back.
Hi.
Galactus will see you.
- I'll go.
- All of you.
You should not have come.
Follow.
Scan everything
and collect samples.
What does Galactus want?
He doesn't want. He feeds.
How does he choose
which planets to consume?
He does not.
You choose.
Yes.
Uh, Johnny.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna charm her.
So what did you say to me?
When you threw me
off your board?
What did you say?
It's a blessing.
It means, "Die with yours."
"Die with yours."
Last question.
So the surfboard, right?
Is that part of your body?
Or is that...
So she dumped you already?
No. It went well.
You stand before Galactus.
The Devourer of Worlds
honors you.
We are honored.
I was once little like you.
Billions of years ago.
A man from another world
before this relentless,
eternal hunger.
You have traveled far.
Yes.
To beg for mercy.
To talk.
You carry the power
to save your world.
Yes. I believe we do.
Inside her.
The child.
- What the hell?
- What...
He hungers.
What does that mean?
I will spare your world.
In exchange for the boy.
What? No.
He possesses the Power Cosmic,
and he will inherit
this cursed throne.
It's not true.
He's- He's normal.
We would know. I would know.
I tested the child.
- He hides his nature from you.
- No.
What are you doing to her?
Baby's coming.
The baby's coming.
- Now?
- Yeah.
You will not have our planet.
And you will never have
our son!
I will eat your planet slowly
while your child watches.
No you don't!
I'm coming, buddy!
Go, go, go, go!
H.E.R.B.I.E., prep all systems
for immediate launch.
No!
Surfboard,
not part of the body.
Come on.
H.E.R.B.I.E.!
Get us out of here, Ben!
Hang in there, Suze,
I'll get you home.
Get us to the FTL!
FTL in visual range.
- Babe.
- I'm here, Sue. I'm here.
Surfer on our six.
Attach then jump.
- And go where?
- Anywhere! Just jump!
H.E.R.B.I.E.,
I'm gonna need your help
stabilizing this thing.
Hold on!
Ben!
We lost her. All clear.
She's still on us.
Johnny, kill her.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She wants to take your nephew.
- Kill her!
- All right. All right.
Just when I finally met
someone interesting.
It's bending the beam!
The wormhole
is bending the beam!
Reed,
I can't get a lock on her!
All right. Figure it out.
Come on.
Reed, what's the plan?
Johnny, quit screwing around.
Do I tell you
how to drive the ship?
Don't tell me
how to kill sexy aliens!
Stop calling her sexy.
- Oh!
- Yes! Yes!
- Yes!
She's back!
- Reed, I can't shake her.
- Working on it!
- She's slippery!
- Reed!
Drop us out of FTL here.
That's a pretty big
neutron star.
I know. We're gonna use it.
Isn't that basically
a black hole?
Won't that kill us?
Taking us out.
What's the plan?
Draw her close enough
to the star,
she'll get stuck
in the gravity well.
There'll be a time dilation.
- How much of a dilation?
- Is it more than mine?
It'll take her a month
to break free.
Take us in, Ben.
Reed, we could get sucked in.
Ben, trust me.
Hang on.
Come on.
It's chewing us up!
Get closer.
A little closer!
Come on, Reed.
What are we doing?
Sue, we need 30 seconds of
invisibility. Can you do it?
After your next contraction.
- Yes!
- Hell, yeah!
You all right, Sue?
We need to strap you down.
- Strapping her down.
- Do not strap me down!
Not strapping her down.
Baby...
- What?
- ...you need gravity to push.
This is not right.
It's not how
it's supposed to be.
I know, I know.
But we're gonna make it work.
You're doing wonderful,
my love.
We don't have enough juice
to get home.
Oh, no.
No, we do not.
I could slingshot
around the star,
draft off
its orbital momentum.
We need to get to
.88 speed of light.
Reed!
- Johnny, the velocity gauge.
- Reed!
On it.
- Oh, don't... don't go.
- I'm here.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Don't go.
I'm right here.
Beginning slingshot.
Here we go.
Coming up on .82.
On your mark, Johnny.
Why...
Why do they wanna take him?
Something is wrong with him.
There's nothing wrong
with him.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do. I do know.
No, you don't.
You know everything,
but you don't know that.
- What if he's a monster?
- He's not a monster.
- Everything's gonna change.
- Nothing is gonna change.
- I promise you.
- I promise.
- You can't promise that.
- Reed...
- Okay.
He's coming. He's coming.
Give me your hand.
.84. Ben!
Come on!
- Sue? Push.
- No.
- Yes, you can.
- .85.
- Ready?
- Okay.
One, two, three, push!
- Come on!
- .86!
Push. Push. That's good.
.87.
- Mark!
- Ben!
H.E.R.B.I.E.
Ben, help!
Thrusters engaged.
H.E.R.B.I.E., get ready!
Hold on, everyone.
I got you, little guy.
Franklin.
There! There! Come on.
I see it!
Wow!
After a monthlong return trip,
the Fantastic Four
are finally home
and receiving a warm welcome.
Oh, my God. Unbelievable.
- Lynne, we're going to need-
- Come this way.
- Reed! Reed!
- Move back!
Dr. Richards,
over here! Can we get a word?
Stand back.
Make a path.
Sue! Sue!
They're ready
for you. Step up.
Just keep it brief.
I'm sorry. We don't have
a prepared statement.
One at a time, please.
One at a time.
Connor.
Welcome back.
Could you take us through
how you defeated Galactus?
How we de...
We didn't.
Not yet. Not yet, we didn't.
What does that mean?
Uh, follow up!
What do you mean, you didn't?
We attempted to negotiate,
but Galactus...
He asked too high a price.
- Well, what does he want?
- What did he ask?
He asked for our child.
What?
He said, "Give us your child,
and I will spare the earth."
We said no, obviously.
We said no.
We're gonna...
We're gonna circle back
with a more
detailed statement...
- You said no?
- What does that mean for us?
Could giving Galactus
the child save us?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hang on- You can't just...
Just answer this. Answer this.
Are we safe?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
You don't know?
What do you mean
you don't know?
I'm sorry. I've failed you.
I need the child.
I must get the child.
But he's just a baby.
He is a being
of infinite power.
One strong enough
to absorb my hunger
so that I may finally rest.
How much time
do we even have?
What do we do
when he gets here?
What about the ship?
We blast it. Problem solved.
You can't blast it.
Conventional weapons
won't work.
- So, we run.
- We run?
Draw him away from Earth.
We're faster than him, right?
- Not faster than the herald.
- We've got a head start.
Yeah, but that's
all we got.
And then he could still
eat the Earth anyways.
Reed?
You wanna take us through
what you have?
- What I have?
- Yeah.
What I have is nothing.
Nothing. Did you say nothing?
I analyzed the samples
H.E.R.B.I.E. took
from Galactus's ship.
All evidence suggests he predates
our universe, our reality.
It could take ten years to
understand his composition,
let alone his existence.
You're talking about a god?
I'm talking about something
beyond our experience.
An unknowable life.
Who imagines Franklin
as his successor
and possessing
some kind of cosmic power.
That can't be true.
You ran all those tests.
Right?
I have, but I don't
know what can or cannot be.
I'm not sure how long.
I'm not sure of anything. I...
I have nothing. I...
I have nothing.
If we could solve something,
any link in the chain...
E is the effort force,
R is the lever arm
connected to the effort.
L is the load,
r is the lever arm
connected to the load.
Archimedes. The Law of Levers.
"Give me a lever
and a place to stand
and I will move the earth."
We need a lever.
You- You wanna
translate that?
Yeah, we solve
the right small problem,
we solve the big Galactus one.
Yes. Yes.
All right, boys,
let's go look for levers.
Yep.
You know,
you're supposed to sleep
when the baby sleeps.
I've been, uh, you know,
reading the books.
He thinks the baby
actually sleeps.
I gotta show you something.
What do you wanna show me?
- It's really good.
- I barely slept last night.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's not like you chose
this whole thing.
Being a mother, you know?
Sit down. Good. I gotta
show you. Just trust me.
Okay. All right.
Johnny, it smells.
It's pheromones. Relax.
All right.
Racking back the helmet cam.
It's a blessing.
It means, "Die with yours."
I told you
I'd heard that before.
Now we have
a sentence translated,
and we can use that to figure
out what all of this means.
I mean, Reed could build
an algorithm, and then...
His big brain is busy.
I'm all over this.
A Rosetta stone to find him
an Archimedes lever.
See?
I can reference old stuff too.
Right. There you go. Good boy.
Fantastic Four has verified
that an unknown spacecraft
believed to be Galactus
has just passed Jupiter.
Financial
institutions remain closed
as angry protestors take to...
The newly
formed Galactus cult intends
to summit Mount Everest.
Tempers boiled
over in Central London today,
breaking out in violence
as the whole world wonders,
"What is to be our fate?"
Hey, what about us?
We got families too.
Guys, it's getting bad
out there.
It seems to me they
have no plan for Galactus.
We, as a society,
have to reckon with the idea
that the Fantastic Four
could save us today,
- but they choose not to?
- No.
The idea is simple.
Reed Richards and Sue Storm
hand over their baby,
and we all live.
One life-
Where are you?
Get down from your high tower.
You're supposed to protect us.
Give up the baby!
- They're scared.
- Who isn't scared?
That is scary.
Why? They can't hurt us.
Well, it's scary
because they hate us.
They think they might die,
and they hate us for it.
And they hate Franklin.
And they may be right
because right now,
we don't have a workable plan.
The clock is ticking.
So their plan looks good.
It's mathematical,
it's ethical
and it's available.
What are you saying?
I'm not saying anything.
Oh, sweetheart.
It's all right, buddy.
All right.
You know, Ben's wrong.
There's always people
that can hurt you.
Sue, please hear me.
I would never
give him up to Galactus.
I would never do that.
"Mathematical? Ethical?
Available?"
It was just so easy
for you to say that.
It means nothing.
It means I know you.
I know how your brain works.
It means you've
thought about it.
It means you've rolled it
around in your head,
and you worked the problem.
Which means nothing.
It is my job
to think terrible things
so that terrible things
don't happen.
It's not your job, Reed.
That's you.
Okay. You're right, it is me.
I don't dream. I don't wonder.
I invite the worst
possible thing into my head
to figure out how to hurt them
before they hurt anybody else.
And you know what?
Sometimes
Sometimes,
you being you hurts me.
Well, I don't mean to.
I know. I know.
I know.
Listen, I am going
to solve this.
I'm gonna make it right.
Hmm.
We don't know what he is
or what he might become
but I am not giving him up.
You're selfish.
How can you
bring him out here?
I wanted to introduce you
to someone.
This is our son, Franklin.
There's been a lot
of talk about him.
Um...
Most of you know me.
You know my story.
When Johnny and I were kids,
our parents were in a car crash.
Our dad was driving
and he lived,
but our mom didn't.
I know what it's like to be part
of a family that was torn apart.
Our dad, he wasn't always a great father,
but he wanted to be.
He did his best.
He wanted us to be together
because that's what family is.
It's about fighting for
something bigger than yourself.
It's about connecting to
It's about having something
bigger than yourself.
And the four of us...
the four of us already do
because we have you.
You know, our mom
always used to say,
"Suzie, for you, I would
move heaven and earth."
And we would do that for you.
I will not sacrifice my child
for this world.
But I will not sacrifice
this world for my child.
We will face this together.
We will fight this together.
And we will defeat
this together.
As a family.
Mmm.
"As a family."
Archimedes.
The Law of Levers.
"Give me a lever and a place to
stand and I will move the earth."
We are going to move
heaven and earth.
Well, just earth.
Sue?
You solved it.
I did?
Yes.
We are going to move Earth
to a place that Galactus
will never find us.
How?
Well,
we already have the lever.
The bridge.
The bridge is a prototype.
You moved an egg
across the room.
You think you can do that
with a planet?
We are out of options.
We have to make it work.
We will make it work.
Heaven and earth.
We interrupt this program
with a special report.
And now an announcement
from Reed Richards.
As you're about to see,
we've solved the physics of teleportation.
H.E.R.B.I.E.
The difference between a planet
and an egg is only scale.
Starting immediately,
we will create teleportation
bridges spanning the globe.
They will be synchronized
and interconnected,
capable of transporting our
planet to a new solar system
within a 2% margin
of the inhabitable zone.
But more importantly,
away from Galactus
where he won't be able to find
us for millions of years.
Time is not on our side.
I'm reaching out to the world
with a list of materials
that we need in bulk.
Plutonium-239.
Plutonium...
All right, people.
Like my old man used to say,
"If you don't know what to do,
pick up a shovel."
Fire it up. We got bridges
to build. Let's go.
The last 36 hours has seen
an historical mobilization
of every country
working together,
in a way the world
has never seen before.
With Galactus's ship
deep within our solar system
and the Fantastic Four's
Hail Mary in the balance,
we are calling
on every helping hand.
If you can do something well,
now you can do it
for your planet.
We are getting reports
that Galactus has passed Mars.
H.E.R.B.I.E., record.
It takes too much power.
I only got this to work
by tripling my intake,
which drained the New York
City grid in two seconds.
To do this, there isn't enough
power in the world.
I'd have to turn off every
light switch on the planet.
For how long?
Factoring in we gotta
keep building bridges,
how long would we need
to conserve power?
Sacrifices
will be made.
We all need to conserve power at
a scale never attempted before.
Quite right, H.E.R.B.I.E.
All the power.
The worldwide energy curfew
only works
if everybody does their part
to conserve electricity.
Ooh, missed a spot.
Yeah, curfew fried it.
Now I look like an idiot.
Beard could be cool.
Seriously?
I built this to see
what you looked like.
You see,
most fathers want their sons
to look exactly like them,
inside and out.
But...
I don't want you
to be like me.
There's something wrong
with me, always has been.
The more I look at you,
the less I know.
And the less I know,
the more scared I am.
So you know what?
I'm not gonna look anymore.
I'm gonna let you tell me
who you are.
And if you'd like to tell me
now, that would be helpful,
especially if you're
an all-powerful space god.
I'd like to know that sooner rather
than later, if you don't mind.
Hmm.
Oh, no.
You're busy peeing.
You're a very good boy.
Thanks, buddy.
This is going to work.
It has to.
Yes! Yes!
Uh... Oh.
Yep, coming.
Coming, coming, coming.
Guys, I am onto something.
Moving a planet here, Johnny.
Yeah, Johnny. It's four.
Fantastic Four.
Let's move a planet.
- Cool beard.
- You mean that? Thank you.
Copy, Delhi.
Let's do this.
London, stand by.
Yes, copy, London.
Copy, Paris.
- Lima, do you copy?
- Copy, Rome.
- Copy, Delhi.
- Copy, Vienna.
Copy, Prague.
Chicago, stand by.
Copy, Chicago.
Earth go for countdown.
Here we go, folks.
Go.
20, 19...
18, 17, 16...
15, 14, 13...
12...
11...
10, 9, 8...
7, 6...
- What is that?
- What's happening?
- She's going for this bridge.
- No.
She's coming for Franklin.
- Oh, my God.
- Lock the building down!
Wait. Where's Johnny?
- Shalla-Bal.
Shalla-Bal!
How do you know that name?
And how did you get these?
How?
He barely has a grasp
of the English language.
Twenty-three transmissions,
all in your language,
trace back
to the planet Zenn-La.
Your home.
They were looking for you,
to thank you.
Once I translated one phrase,
I pieced together
enough language
to understand
a part of your history.
You were some sort of
scientist or astronomer.
When Galactus came, you
offered to serve as his scout
if he'd spare your planet.
Was it to spare your family?
He turned you into this.
Shalla-Bal.
Those were messages from the
one planet Galactus spared.
Your planet.
These planets
weren't so lucky.
How many
do you remember, Shalla-Bal?
Proxima Delphi. Saigas.
Do you remember Polaris?
They begged for mercy.
You brought Galactus
to all of these planets.
And now
you're bringing him here,
to my home, to my family!
Just trying to save my world,
you know,
like you did.
So give up the child.
If he was older,
he would do it himself.
Like I did.
So take me.
Take me.
Not the boy.
Let me make the sacrifice.
It's not yours to make.
Then stay and help us.
There is no help.
Take the child
and leave this doomed place.
Maybe you'll live long enough
to forgive yourselves.
- Johnny, that was incredible.
- I mean, does it even matter?
You saved Franklin.
Yes, it matters.
Reed?
We're not leaving, are we?
No. No, we're not.
We're not leaving.
Um- Uh, yeah. Same here.
You gotta give us a second.
Um...
Yeah, this is Johnny Storm.
Can you hear me?
The line's too busy.
- I'm sorry, okay?
- This is London.
- This is London. Do you copy?
- Hold, London.
What's going on?
Hold, Paris.
Paris, hold.
The line's not very clear.
- Can you say that again?
- Hold the line.
Chicago, yes, we're onto it.
We're just, uh-
We're fixing the problem.
We're trying to get, uh...
We're trying
to get on top of this.
- Sydney, stand by.
- Yep. Got it.
- Tokyo, stand by.
- Hold. Hold.
We have to bring him here.
- We are aware.
- Yes, I understand.
- Can you stand by?
- We are aware.
- I'll update you.
- Yeah. Yeah.
We need to
bring Galactus here.
I will come back
to you. Hold.
- Call you back.
- Hold up.
Reed?
We need Galactus to come here?
I feel like we just spent a lot of time
trying to prevent that from happening.
Listen to me. We need to
get him away from his ship.
We need to bring him here,
to Times Square.
And then what?
And then, instead of moving
a planet away from one giant,
we move one giant
away from the planet.
If we route every power grid
on the Eastern Seaboard,
through our one last bridge,
charge back up,
we can keep
the portal open for...
Thirty-seven seconds.
Thirty... Not a lot of time
to throw a space god
off a planet.
- No, it is not.
- And where do we send him?
To the far edges
of the universe.
Without a ship,
he'll be stranded.
How are we supposed to
get Galactus to Times Square?
And how do we move one giant
through one large bridge?
I haven't figured
that part out yet.
You have.
Have what?
We have to use the only thing
Galactus wants.
No. I'll think of another way.
- What are you talking about?
- You can't.
You can't think
of another way.
- I will.
- There is only one way.
What are you talking about?
We have to use Franklin.
Yes.
You wanna use the boy?
You wanna use the boy as bait.
- No.
- That's your plan?
No, it's not my plan.
It's our plan.
It's the only plan.
It's not my plan.
I hate that plan.
- It's a bad plan. Stupid plan.
- Terrible idea.
Why don't I just burn through his ship?
That's another plan.
He's your kid
we're talking about.
Sue.
- I know.
- Sue. Sue.
Yes, I know. I know. I know!
I thought this was one of the most
beautiful things we'd ever built.
Feels terrifying now.
It can be beautiful again.
Everything can.
They've been gone a while.
Johnny.
Go check. See if they're back.
I'm in no rush to do that.
Well, I'm definitely not
gonna check.
I'm definitely
not going either.
Thank you
for going and checking.
You're welcome.
It's the least I could do
to say thank you for
going down to check first.
I'm definitely not going down.
- Chickenshits.
- Jesus.
Don't do that.
- I hate it when you do that.
- Don't do that.
Come on.
Let's run through the details.
I don't like
when she does that.
It's like...
It's unsettling when people
just appear like that.
Bombproof. Shockproof.
Radiation-proof.
Franklin will go here
when Galactus arrives.
Hey, do we know what direction
Galactus will be coming from?
Well, it could be
from anywhere.
But when he crosses
those lines, we trigger it.
We're in
the very center of the city.
We're surrounded by
miles of apartment buildings.
Any path he takes,
he's gonna be going through
thousands and thousands
of families.
I got an idea you'll hate.
Oh, my.
Very advanced.
So this must be
where the sausage is made.
I think I prefer just trying
to steal the sausage.
Please, don't touch.
Oh!
We'll fix that.
The...
Harvey.
Hello there, little robot man.
Could you dim the lights
for me, please?
Harvey, we wanted
to ask you something.
And whatever it is,
I would like him to ask me.
It's not-
It's not Reed or me asking.
It's the entire planet asking.
It wouldn't be the entire
planet now, would it?
Just the over part.
No, Mr. Elder.
We've met Galactus.
He'll eat
the under part first.
Well, regardless,
why don't you butter me up?
Spread it on.
- Okay, Mole Man.
- Mole Man?
You touch another piece
of my-
- Enough.
- Take the "mole" out of it.
- It's Mr. Elder to you.
- That is enough.
Give us a minute.
Just give us a minute.
Yes, that's it.
Johnny, don't be mad.
I didn't dress you.
Don't listen to him.
You're handsome.
Harvey.
I'm sorry, Sue. I'm...
End of days.
We all gotta learn
how to laugh.
So what do you need?
Evacuation orders
are in effect
in the Greater New York area.
Please report to Subterranea.
Evacuation orders
are in effect
in the Greater New York area.
Please report to Subterranea.
Welcome to Subterranea.
Hello there.
Welcome, sunshiners.
Thank you so much.
Yes, do me a favor and just
wipe your feet upon entry.
I'm kidding. It's all dirt.
Please, keep a move on.
Good evening. We,
the people of Earth, prepare
for what could be
our final moments.
The hours ahead may feel long,
but we must use them
to support each other.
And we must hope.
We must dare to hope.
Hey, Mrs. H.
- Let me help you with that.
- Oh, thank you, Ben.
We must use the time wisely
to be with the ones
we cherish.
Keep hope, all right?
What?
Um, sorry, just... Hi.
- Hey.
Uh, you're looking
very distinguished.
I'm surprised
to see you here. I...
Did you come
for spiritual guidance?
Oh, no, no.
I just came to see you.
I leave you
tonight with these words.
"Never doubt
that a small group
of thoughtful,
committed citizens
can change the world.
Indeed, it's the only thing
that ever has."
Positions.
Hmm.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Don't cry.
I'll be back in a minute,
little guy.
Just a couple more steps.
Come on, come on.
Clever little bugs.
He's going for Franklin.
Light him up, Johnny.
Ben!
Oh, my God.
What time is it, Ben?
No.
- What time is it, Ben?
- No, Johnny.
- Say it!
- I don't wanna.
Say it!
It's clobberin' time!
You are my salvation.
My deliverance
from this vicious hunger.
Time to feed.
Put down my son.
Sue. Sue, stop.
Sue, stop. It's too much.
- Get Franklin.
- Sue, stop!
Save our son.
Johnny, the controls.
Ah!
Hang on, Suze!
Johnny, now!
Reed! It worked.
No!
Tell Franklin
Uncle Johnny loves him.
Sue.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
- I got him. I got him.
- Sue.
No. No. Sue. Sue.
- She breathing?
- No.
No. No, baby. No.
You stay with us.
You stay with us, okay?
Stay with me, Sue.
Stay with us, baby.
Come on, Sue.
Come on, Sue, stay with us.
Don't leave us.
Sue!
Come on, baby!
I'm sorry.
Hey.
He's not us. He's more.
Wow, folks.
We have so much exciting
ground to cover today.
In the last year,
a lot has happened.
We have seen it
with our own eyes,
but tonight, we're gonna
see it through theirs.
Our city, our country
and our planet...
No. And there's nothing
to be nervous about.
You know,
you just stick with me.
This thing will be done
before we know it.
...obvious to say,
but it is definitely worth talking about,
is the fact that the surfboard
is not part of the body.
Okay, so,
Ted wanted me to give you
something as a thank-you
- for doing this.
- Oh.
Interesting.
He would love it if Franklin
would wear it
for this in one minute.
- No, actually.
- No. Absolutely not.
No, I don't think we can.
Well,
I will break the bad news.
- Thank you, Lynne.
- You're welcome.
Places, please.
- It's too early.
- Way too early.
It's too early for
that kind of stuff.
He can't even sit up
without help.
I did not have time to eat
breakfast this morning...
So if only I could eat
a magic baby.
Get his hair.
Get that hair, yeah.
No. Don't... Don't try me.
Who knows where
his powers will take him?
But right now, he's here.
What's that guy doing?
- Who's that right there?
- Hi, cutie.
Frankie.
You got him?
Explorers, heroes,
citizens or leaders.
They continue to change,
becoming whatever we need
them to be whenever we need.
- We're going in ten...
- Ladies and gentlemen,
just when you thought
we couldn't love, admire
or appreciate them
any more than we do...
...and they're now
25% more fantastic...
...Reed, Sue,
Johnny, Ben and Franklin,
the Fantastic Five!
Precious cargo.
Coming through.
Is this...
- No, I've set that already.
- You've already set it?
Let's get this car seat
in nice.
All right, just make sure
that it...
- Hold on, wait. Set the...
- Right, pull up.
I gotta set it in first
before you close it.
- Set it in before you...
- There.
It's gonna make that noise
until you thread
- the belt under the chair...
- All right.
...and then you get it
through the other side.
You gotta
feed it through.
Yeah. I'm doing it.
- Well, I don't feel anything.
- I can't...
- You just hook it under the...
- It's through. It's through.
- All right, I got it.
- Through the buckle.
Let's move this along,
fellas.
You gotta thread it.
You gotta...
That isn't gonna help.
You gotta thread it through,
connect it
- and then pull the slack.
- I've thread it through.
- It's threaded through.
- You didn't pull the slack.
Just push from above.
Push from above.
- No, you gotta...
- Pull the slack!
Okay, I'll get-
I've pulled the slack.
It's thread through.
- All right.
- I can't fit my hands in.
You from the left.
You from above.
Three, two, one.
- Oh! Yes! Yes!
- That's a good sound.
Okay, we're ready.
♪ Fantastic Four! ♪
"He pushed his way out
and..."
- "...he was a butterfly."
- "A butterfly."
Oh. Mmm.
You want the other book,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Back in a second, babe.
H.E.R.B.I.E., have you seen
the book that Franklin loves?
Not that one.
We did that one yesterday,
and I know he loves it,
but thi...
Here we are. It's here.
We're going for something
a little bit more fun today.
Yeah?
♪ Changed by
Cosmic rays from space ♪
♪ Now they save
The human race ♪
♪ Sue Storm
Commands the light ♪
♪ Johnny's flames
Burn blazing bright ♪
♪ Ben is rocking the world
With might ♪
♪ And Reed bends science
Left and right ♪
It's Red
Ghost and his Super-Apes!
It's clobberin' time!
♪ Join the fight
And even the score ♪
♪ Get ready to watch ♪
♪ Fantastic Four ♪